Good evening everyone! The morning chime has sounded.
We are Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
We look forward to working with you.
Please give us your best regards.
So, before we start the program, we would like to decide who will be today's MC.
Please vote for 1 or 2, whichever you prefer.
The person holding the number card with that number on it is today's MC.
So, let the voting begin!
Okay, then. That way.
Okay.
Are you sure? Really.
Okay, Sakurai, this way.
Yuna,
Wait.
Are you okay?
I did everything.
Be careful.
I'm always warned about this.
You know, Yuna only goes to the showroom with me.
Well, not only with me, but also with Nonaka-chan, to be exact, but when I do the showroom, Emma is always there.
You said that today, too.
Five, four, three, two, one.
The result is open!
You must be Kim. Japanese.
You're so Kim, aren't you?
Okay, here we go. Ready.
Sakurai.
Emma.
Yes, I'm here.
Oh, I almost went ahead without permission.
I'm sorry, please.
So, I am the one who is acting as the number 2,
I will be the MC today.
I look forward to working with you.
I am Emma Sakurai and I will be your MC today,
I am number 17, Yuna Nakamura.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
So, that's it,
Today's,
Ebichu's pleasant and fufufu showroom.
Yay!
Today, the 76th EBITCHU's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Ebichu's Delightful Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Uka-san's showroom.
Yes, I know, I know.
So, I would like to go to a spread time here.
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this distribution,
I'm going to ask you to make an announcement on the official X of Ebichu now.
Please do so.
What are you going to do?
Let's go. Yes, Jill. Thank you very much.
Please spread the word.
Yes, and, you know..,
Yes, and what a week,
What is it?
It's the SHOWROOM Christmas Special, and we have a Christmas present for all of you who are watching.
Yay!
That's right, the top three in the ranking,
We're going to give away autographed checkers of Emayuna, who is performing today.
Are you sure?
Are you sure? Really.
Thank you very much.
Please take the picture in this outfit,
Yes, this is for the rankings we will read out at the end of the show.
Last minute giving may not be reflected,
So, please give early.
Please do so.
Yes, please look forward to it until then.
So, today's topic is the following,
A “Yuukai de Fuwa Fuwa” survey.
Yes.
There are a lot of questions this time, aren't there?
That's right.
Please take a look.
Let's see.
(1)
What's that?
(1) Um, that's exactly what it is. Christmas arts and crafts 2024
2) Honorifics lesson
3) I want to fix my fast speech
(4) Chocolate addiction
5) Restlessness of the mouth
(6) Nostalgia championship
Oh, wow. Almost....a championship of things I've missed. Oh, wow. Yes.
Almost all of them are free.
That's right. That's unusual, only one.
So, will you choose one?
I'd like you to choose.
Okay, let's start!
Well, I don't know, but I think the first one is this one.
Well, I think everyone wants to hear this one.
Sure, sure, sure.
The second one is, let's see.... Oh, sorry, number 2 is an English lesson.
It's all about the mouth, isn't it?
Four more consecutive mouths.
Mouth, mouth, mouth.
Indeed.
Go!
Three.
End
I don't know.
After all, it is No. 1.
Christmas University Welcome Party 2024
How was it?
We talked at a lot of places.
It was fun. It was a lot of fun. It was. It was fun, it was a lot of fun. Yeah.
Yeah.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun. It sure was.
For the first time in, what, years?
It's the Christmas arts and crafts festival.
It's been six years.
Wow.
It's been 2018.
So, you, uh, well, you love Christmas, right?
I know.
You know what?
I love Christmas, I really do.
I understand. I love the atmosphere, I love the presents, I love Christmas.
And how happy I am to be able to do a Christmas concert on that day!
I really do!
I love Christmas too.
I love the end of the year.
You know what I mean.
I love New Year's Eve, New Year's Eve.
I understand.
I love the costumes, too,
Maya-san thinks of outfits that suit this girl.
Yes, yes.
It was from the members, wasn't it?
Maya did,
YUNA is not wearing milk tea this time, but champagne gold.
Wow!
Yay!
That's so cool! What's that?
Champagne gold idol.
That's so cool.
Champagne gold.
It's like Christmas, isn't it?
That's right. It's all a little shiny.
Yeah, yeah. It's true, it's true.
I'm champagne gold.
It's a shiny champagne gold with a milk tea sheen.
Indeed. It was pretty.
It was cute.
Oh, and your jacket...what do you call it?
You know, the jacket.
The jacket was too cute,
But, you know, we used to do sing-alongs with that every time.
Jacket, jacket.
And, you know, there's a part in the sing-along where you put your hands in the air like this,
The sleeves of that jacket are very voluminous,
I know, I know.
It's shiny.
When you lift it up like this, it's like it has three faces.
It's like there are three faces,
It's interesting.
It's funny. I was giggling a little myself.
I was laughing a little myself,
I know what you mean.
I know what it's like to bump into someone with my arms.
I know, I know. But it's my favorite. I love it.
It was fun.
That's just like Mayama-san.
Mayama-san.
That's Mayama-san.
How was it, everyone?
How was it?
I got to hear a lot of my favorite songs.
Indeed.
I think you got to hear the song you wanted to hear.
The opening movie was really cute, wasn't it?
They were so cute.
You know, they are waiting in the back, right?
Yes, that's right.
Just who was it?
But she was there from the very beginning.
Yeah, she was there from the beginning.
I had never seen their faces on such a big screen before,
I was nervous.
It was a little embarrassing.
It was embarrassing.
I was nervous, but I was also nervous. It was embarrassing.
I kind of like the other members, I think they're cute, but I'm embarrassed that I like them a little bit,
I'm embarrassed that I like them a little bit.
That's true.
The place where we shot the opening orb was really beautiful,
It was really beautiful.
It was so beautiful.
You don't usually go to places like that, do you?
No, I don't.
It was so beautiful, I was so happy.
You said you were looking at my account earlier.
I'm so happy.
It ends tomorrow.
It ends tomorrow. I hope you all enjoy it.
Please look at it a lot. I want you to see it. I'll watch it too. It's about time. It ends tomorrow. I hope you all will see it.
I'll see it too.
They'll be here soon.
It's coming soon.
The unit seems to be perfect for her.
Chika, I also want to say something,
I was a runner for Fuyukoi and Zenryoku Runner,
I played Zenryoku Runner with Fuyuki when my sister did it,
Kao-chan, right?
Kao-chan, this is it, right?
What? ! I thought, “What? I thought, “Wow!
I was like, “What? I was like, “Oh, my God!
Emma and Yuna were just at rehearsal,
Emma and Yuna were right at the same place on the bottom and in the hair.
When Kao-chan did it quickly at the rehearsal,
Yuna and Yuna! I was like, “What?
What? What?
Huh?
That's what I told him yesterday.
Oh, shit. Sorry, sorry.
What? This proves that it's really true.
Yeah, it does.
That was really cool.
I'm sure it was.
And this.
Huh? Oh, yeah?
What is it? Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee! I really want to be made to do it.
I really want it. It's nice, isn't it?
It was cool, wasn't it?
It was cool.
There were so many things going on,
You know.
I don't think I'll get bored even if I look at the archives.
Yes, I guess so. Please look at it.
Please take a look.
Thank you very much.
Shall we move on? Shall we go next?
Okay.
Well, let's start again.
Start.
I'm getting bitter.
That's right.
I'm going to be sick.
The opening V was cool, too.
He was handsome, wasn't he?
It's already in the first part. I'm sorry. Mr. Ikebayashi. He was so cool. He was handsome, wasn't he? This is the first part.
Mr. Ikebayashi.
He's in charge of melody.
That's for sure.
Is that Kazuki Double Eye? This is Santa Claus.
Indeed.
Go!
Four, three, two, one.
What's that?
There's a lot of freebies.
Yeah.
What is it?
Oh?
Six, the nostalgia championship.
Oh!
We were doing this earlier. It's a lot of fun.
Yeah.
I forgot the title.
Yeah, um, the title?
Um..,
I miss it.
It was difficult. It was difficult, because when we were talking about what we wanted to talk about in M.I.N.A.
We were both born in 2007.
It's been 17 years or so.
That's right.
I'm telling you, we've been alive for about 17 years.
I may say “07” every time, but you know,
I may be saying “07” every time, but when I say I was born in 2007, people say, “Oh, it's only yesterday.
Yes, that's what people say.
I've been alive for 17 years.
That's right, don't talk about our 17 years.
Well, yes, and the two of us who were born in '07 were nostalgic,
We were talking about the things we missed, the things we used to watch back then,
We were talking about the things we missed, the things we used to watch back then, and we found that we were watching the same things.
I thought that would be very exciting, so I wondered if you would understand.
Surprisingly, yes,
I'm sure. I can understand something that has been going on for a long time.
But on the other hand, they might not even know if it's something we said.
That's right. It could go either way.
Emma and I hit it off best with Lulu and Lala,
There was a novel and a book called Lulu and Lala,
I went to the bookstore and checked out a book called Lulu and Lala, in which two girls named Lulu and Lala cook.
Do you guys know that?
Well, I don't think I'm going to get it.
What, Lulu and Lara was that long ago?
No, Gris and Gras.
Gris and Gras.
But I don't know.
Because, you know, Lulu and Lara was a beautiful book in the library.
Yes, that's true.
So I have a feeling that it's a recent book.
I don't know that one. I only know Guri and Gura. Yes, that's true. So, I have a feeling that this is a recent book. He doesn't know that one.
He only knows Guri and Gura.
But it's close.
Yes, it is.
It's not so different.
I only know Emma and Yuna.
I only know Emma and Yuna. That's for sure.
I'm glad.
They look so much alike. Yuna and Emma.
Hmm?
I knew I didn't catch that.
I knew I didn't know.
I don't know.
Dad, where's the switch?
I love it.
You put a little circle on the box of Kleenex and you push it, and your dad does what you tell him to do.
I'll listen to your orders.
I knew it. It says “Grand Master '06” on it.
You know... maybe someone who went to elementary school with him can tell?
I guess so.
That's why.
I know.
I know the father switch.
You know the father switch? I've been doing this dad switch thing for a while.
What about the design? You seem to know a lot about design.
I don't know what else to say. I've done it, I've done it, I've done it, I've done it, I've done it.
But it's like... you don't know anything about it.
That's true.
I loved it.
Why? Why is it so addictive?
John from TV, we know.
Yes, we know.
You don't know?
I know! It's done, it's done. You don't know?
But you know a lot about design, don't you? Everyone does.
Everyone says they don't know it.
I like that one. PACCOLORIN.
PACCOLORIN! The round, square, and triangle character.
Do you know it? PACCOLORIN.
I wonder if the round one is the youngest.
I guess he's not the youngest.
He was cute. Like Yuna.
What? But, you know, it's done. Like Yuna. Huh?
But it's done. I don't know.
Hey, they don't know.
On the contrary, this is the least I've ever felt from Gene.
That's for sure.
On the contrary, I'd like to hear, “Do you know this? I'd like to hear you say, “Do you know this? I'd like to hear from everyone.
I'd like to hear suggestions from everyone,
We know about this?
Okay, now for the game.
The person who can comment on something that M.A.N.A. misses wins,
Even if you are from a different generation than us, if you can be, you win.
That's good.
I want you to be 17 years old.
Like 17 years ago.
Sure, like 17 years ago, or 15 years ago.
Sure. I don't know about 17 years ago.
Sure.
Mini.
Mini 4.
Mini 4. What, something like a Tomica?
What? How do you know?
Maybe I've heard of it.
Mini 4.
Sleep!
I know sleep.
I love it.
It's not a generation thing. It's a language textbook.
Yes, it is. That lone red one.
I think I know the three freshmen.
I don't know them.
What?
Two of them are Pretty Cure.
Well, they're Precure.
They're not Girisedai. Yokai Watch is Dosedai.
Hey. I watched it so much.
It's amazing. Like Koma-san.
Oh, Ganko-chan came out, right?
Isn't the hand spinner amazing?
He's so good.
He's really good. Oh, no! Oh, man! Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
Wow, this guy is amazing.
Oh, my God.
Love & Billy are a little sissy.
Wait, Jewel Watch is bad.
What's that? The one that looks like a cat?
I loved Jewel Watch.
I don't know, I've never seen the Jewel Watch.
Really?
I always fall asleep.
There was a game about it, wasn't there? Jewel Watch.
Yes, there was.
Oh, no.
I just got a jolt.
The NES is a little different.
It was a while ago.
A little bit is fine.
I love the longhorned beetle.
Haramekowamushi.
Like Ojarumaru. Like Ojarumaru.
I watched Ojarumaru.
Oshiri Tantei is bad.
He was showing them. Three Jewels.
The Three Jewels catalog is more exciting than anything else.
You know what I mean?
I was looking at them so much.
Now that I think about it, it's not good, is it?
They have rubber bands for a penny, don't they?
Five, one, three, five.
I really liked that last page. I know. I used to look at it a lot. It's so bad when you think about it, there's a rubber band for a penny. 5, 1, 3, 5.
I really liked that last page.
I was looking at it so much.
I was looking at the solution.
It's amazing.
You know what's fun about the three jewels?
I love when I find something I like in the catalog and I work really hard to write down the numbers on a piece of paper,
I love it when I find something I like in the catalog and write the number down on a piece of paper.
Cute, huh?
CLAIRE'S.
Remember Squeeze?
Yup.
Squeeze, Claire's.
What's the intonation?
Claire's.
I loved it.
Oh, Claire's. I loved it, Mom.
I don't know, but Claire's, you know, there's not a lot of places like Claire's, you know.
That's why I met Haraji-kun, right?
I remember going there when I first came to Tokyo.
He said, “Claire's is cute.
Cute.
I've heard of them.
But we all have.
Let's play the game of saying you miss everything, and then covering your bottom.
Sure, you'll wear the bottom of your head no matter what you say.
In a manner of speaking, we're pretty much alive. We are, too.
Higashimurayama temperature is fun, isn't it?
I used to do this a lot.
I used to do it in a circle with everyone at school.
It was so much fun.
It's a game that is popular during recess at school.
It was very popular.
Ping.
Ping,
Ping is bad.
Ping is in the shape of a bird.
Bird?
I know what a ping is.
You know what it is?
It's not a penguin.
Yes, it is.
Pingu doesn't talk.
Oh, really?
That's right. Hexagon? It's like Hexagon Gymnastics. Heh. Yes, that's right.
Hexagon?
Something like Hexagon Gymnastics.
That's true.
But you know, for a while, something like this, like Hexagon, was popular.
A game called Hexagon.
Yeah, it was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun, wasn't it?
It's not gymnastics.
It's something.
It was fun.
It was a little before today's radio calisthenics.
Hexagon Gymnastics.
Hexagon Gymnastics was scientifically proven to be useless, so a new one was introduced.
There was a game called “Ito's Family Dining Table,” wasn't there?
Me too. Ito Family's Table.
I wish I could have seen it in the past.
I might understand.
I worked really hard to make and serve omu-rice with this.
She worked really hard.
The serving side.
That's right.
I couldn't surround it.
I'm still at the level.
I couldn't sleep.
That's right, that's right.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not sure I can do it.
Hexagon Gymnastics is badass.
Hey...
IQ Supplement is a little bit dangerous.
I miss IQ Supplement.
You used to use it a lot.
Indeed.
IQ supplements.
I used to take a lot of them to get smarter.
That's for sure.
You couldn't get them for a while, right?
Yes, I couldn't get them. Sweat of death.
That's for sure.
I love YO-SAMA. That's for sure. Yo-Sama.
I loved it.
Yo-Sama, you divide 10 into 4 and 6 and calculate. There was the cherry calculation, right?
When you add 10, for example, when you add 6 and 10, you add 6 and 4 to make 10.
When I was in elementary school, an uncle came to teach me that.
He told me to remember “yosama,” which means to divide the sum into 4 and 6.
He told me to remember “Yosama,” and I looked up “4-sama” as hard as I could.
Oh, what? Really? Did it come up?
Yes, I know the 4-sama.
I do.
That's why I was able to do the cherry calculation.
Wow.
Six means four.
I see.
Yes, I can understand the 4.
Is it only 4 and 6?
Because, but, I don't know.
I'm sure.
I don't remember what you mean a little bit.
Zugudan-bun-bun.
“Zu-dan-dan-dan.
Oh, wait. I was just thinking that.
I've heard of this before, haven't I?
Zugudan-bun-bun-bun game.
No, but it's tough, isn't it?
We all competed with each other to see how fast we could say it.
Bobo-bo-bo. Bobo-bobo-bobo-bobo.
This is too appropriate. blah, blah, blah. No, you mean actually doing it, right? Bobo-bobo-bobo? Bobo-bobo-bobo is fun, right?
It's fun. It's refreshing to be able to say it.
Yeah.
The world of pot arts.
Oh, no, I mentioned something.
World pot arts?
When hot men around the world cook hot pot.
I miss it. I miss it.
I miss it.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Would you like to go for one more?
Would you like to go on for one more?
Is this going to be the last one?
All right, let's get started!
Start, start, start. Is this going to be a whole topic? All right, let's go! Start, start, start!
I wonder what it's all about.
Sure, I'm curious about all of it.
But it's all connected.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, five, four, three, two, one.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
I had a hard time getting into it today.
What is it, what is it, what is it? I wonder.
Yes, what is it?
Number 2. A lesson on honorifics.
I don't understand this.
It's about Aima Sakurai.
Yes, this is Sakurai,
I went to school the other day and did a lesson in Japanese, like a review of honorifics. In the class, we learned the honorifics that can be used when you work or have a part-time job.
We had never had a part-time job before, so we thought it would be kind of fun.
Sounds fun.
So today I asked Yuna to do it as a customer,
Emma is going to be the shopkeeper.
I mean, the customers don't have to be so polite, right?
But I would like Yuna to do it too.
Okay.
May I ask you to use honorifics?
Yes, you may.
So, where's the store?
Clang, clang, clang, clang, clang.
Anywhere is fine.
Okay, convenience store.
Convenience store.
Krang-krang-krang.
Welcome. A convenience store. Okay, convenience store. At the convenience store. Yes, Karankarankarankarankarankarankarankarankarank.
Welcome.
Convenience store? Really a convenience store?
Please feel free to use it.
Looks like an apparel store.
Please come in.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I'm looking for the raffle tickets that went on sale today.
Yes, they are. We're running low right now and out of stock.
It went on sale today.
It's a little late. The customer came a little late,
If they had come a little earlier, we would have had some in stock,
It's a pity.
We may have something else in stock.
I have really studied the practice.
Yes, I have.
Sorry.
This is a great lawsuit.
I just got scratched by a fingernail.
But I'll call it a minor accident.
First of all, I think it's wrong to work part-time at a convenience store.
Is it difficult?
Convenience store workers don't talk much, do they?
Yes, it is.
What's the best place? What's the best?
What's the best place?
Show me your example, Yuna.
Okay, what do you think of the apparel?
Oh, yes, I'm good.
Do you like apparel? Okay, then. Okay. Okay, I'll go.
Welcome.
You're cute.
Excuse me, I'd like to try on some clothes,
Is that okay?
Just one item?
Yes.
Then it's fine. Go ahead.
Is that okay?
Yes.
They're here. They're here.
Really? What do you think? This one. It's cute. May I? Yes, it's here. Here it comes. Are you sure? This one.
It's cute.
Really? It looks great on you.
By the way, how do you think it would look cute with this?
What do you think?
It's a magic item that you can match with anything you own to make it look cute.
I see.
By the way, what are you doing today?
She is working today. Watching.
Like looking.
I'm working like I'm watching.
Really?
I am working.
That's great.
By the way, do you have any recommendations for this?
Colors.
Color.
Which do you think is better, black or brown?
It's brown, isn't it?
Why? It is milk tea brown, isn't it? Why?
It is milk tea color, yes.
Is this correct?
So, it doesn't matter which one is correct.
I want you to tell me what you learned.
If you know what kind of terms you learned.
For example, when a shopkeeper gives you 10,000 yen, you often say, “I will take it from 10,000 yen.
But I don't need “from 10,000 yen,” he says.
Because you want to learn it.
It's a long way to go from trying on clothes, not from the cash register.
I don't want the biggest sky.
So that's how it is.
Oh, let's make “I had dinner with Mayama” an honorific.
Well, let me just say that I learned to use the honorific “I ate mayama for dinner”.
Let's see, “Mayama-sama-sama,” or “Mayama-sama,” or “Mayama-sama,” or “Mayama-sama,” or “Mayama-sama. Mayama-san ate rice.
Oh, but I wonder if it's something different.
Eh, I don't know.
Mayama-sama..,
Don't you want to see the “Mr. Mayama”?
Mayama-san ate his rice.
May I say something?
Yes, you may.
May I cool it down? May I answer too?
Mayama-sama..,
Mr. Moyama has finished his meal.
Oh, my God!
What?
Wow.
The correct answer is, Mr. Moyama ate his meal.
But I was just going to say, I was going to answer you, too,
You don't want Mr. Mayama? Mr. Mayama?
I was getting pretty serious.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Can I have it? I was like, “No, I don't want it.
It's really difficult. Polite, respectful, and humble language.
Yes, that's right. We did that too. At school.
It was difficult.
But, you know, we will be using them more and more.
It's going to be used more and more.
When I first came here, I looked it up on my own, and I thought “huh, I'm doing it,
I don't say “I understand” to adults.
You don't say “ah ah ah” or “thank you” to adults.
I don't use kanji to write “I'll be happy to help you”.
You say, “I will do it in hiragana.
What did you do with the kanji?
I don't know the reason, but if we used them, even if we didn't understand, we wouldn't be offended if we did.
Well, that's certainly important.
That's what I learned.
I learned that.
Sure, there are times when you say, “I understand,” but...,
I understand, but there are a lot of “I understand.
You say, “I understand, sir.
That's right. That's what we do when we contact people.
Yes, we do.
Mayama, I'm sorry, but I use honorifics. Really? Isn't that hard?
MayamaSorry?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I thought you were mad at me, Mayama san.
I'm mad at you, Mayama san,
Mayama san, you're so sweet Mayama san, Mayama san
Very much
Eh, sorry
Mayama san
Mayama Ms. Mayama
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh?
No, Mr. Nakano.
I apologize, Mayama-san.
Correct.
I can't lose with honorifics.
Wait a minute.
What class did you take?
Hey, hey, Mayama.
Mayama, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I was too light.
Mayama, it's Mayama.
Don't say it.
Sorry.
I'm just a little surprised all of a sudden.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
It's so sudden.
I won't clean up.
Hey, I'm not cleaning up.
I miss it.
We were just stepping out together,
What?
You said, “I need your help.
And you were too nervous.
You were too nervous, so you said, “I want you to clean up, but I don't have a sword.
It's the opposite!
When I said that I felt uncomfortable,
I thought it was the opposite of “akura,” so I reworded it correctly.
When you said “kata-keitodoki,” I said “sukerachinai.
When I said “Skeerachinai,” he said “kata-keitodoki,” then I said “skeerachinai.
It was all mixed up, wasn't it?
I was too nervous, but I don't usually use it.
That's right.
I don't know.
But, you know, I don't know if they say “kata-keitodoki” or “kata-keitodoki.
But when you said “sukerachinai,” I was like, “Suke-tachi-nai?
I miss it so much.
I would say it.
I would say it. It was difficult.
I really love that story.
It was nerve-wracking.
Nervous.
Well, that's why I'm going to work harder and harder.
Study English.
Yes, I will. Thank you very much. Thank you all for your time.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so that's all for the survey work of the fortunate couple.
So, that's it,
So, we will continue with the following,
We are going to continue with this project.
The title is “A Joyful and Married Couple's December!
Yay!
In the script, there are various plans for December, written like a restaurant menu,
We will choose the one we like and do it.
Yes, I will.
Yuna-san, there are a lot of them,
Yes.
Is there anything you would like to do?
But, after all, what would you like to do at the end of the year?
The “Valid Word Award”.
Oh!
The EBichu Effective Word of the Year Award.
Let's decide the year 2024 for the EBichu Effective Word of the Year Award.
Oh, I like that.
Well, do you have any?
I definitely have a word for this year.
Yes, I do.
However....
Aaaaah!
There's something in the A melody of “Blue Dijness” that says, “I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it,
When we have a problem in a lesson or something, and we think, “Why don't we do this? But when we have a problem in a lesson or something like that, we say, “Why don't we just do this?
But when it came to “to-woe”, everyone said “to-woe”.
That's true.
Yes, that's right. I might have said that. Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
However....
I'm going to lose it.
If I had said “but,” it would have made things a little tense.
But, “however,” it's a nice touch. It's a good way to keep the magic in place.
Yes, that's for sure.
Kao used to use it in the city.
I like the way Kao's neck moves.
Twier.
Indeed.
Indeed, indeed.
Twier.
I want everyone to use it.
Indeed, yes.
When you're in trouble.
Twier.
Indeed.
Wow.
It's a buzzword for sure.
Is there anything else?
I wonder.
Buzzword?
A word that was popular in Ebichu?
Hmmm...
But...
I don't know.
I've been using it on my own.
I don't know if it was popular in Ebichu.
I was on my own, I don't know if it was popular in Ebituaries, but it was like my own money.
I used my own money, too.
My own money.
Not actual money. Self-financing.
I might have said, “I'm buying with my own money.
Emayma mainly used it when she stopped by to buy something on the way to work, for example,
But I'll pay for it with bullion, so it's OK.
Yes, yes, yes.
Bullion.
Yuno said that too, right?
He did say that.
Oh, with bullion.
Oh, you said it with bullion.
It's not a bullion trap, is it?
With bullion.
It's just that, you know, bullion sounds a bit raw, doesn't it?
It sure does.
Bullion.
How many more are there?
But it's still “bullion,” “twirly bullion,” and “twier.
That's for sure. Twier is good, isn't it?
Twier is very good.
It's addictive.
It becomes a habit. You want to use it.
Indeed, indeed.
The opposite of bullion?
It's already tagane.
Indeed.
Tagane.
Tagane. Tagane, indeed. Tagane.
Yes, indeed.
Indeed, indeed. I hope you will all make one.
Yes.
Well then, the Trending Words Tabletop 2014 has just ended like this,
Then, Sakurai, may I choose one?
Please go ahead.
I really like your pictures, Yuna-san.
Thank you very much.
So let's exchange drawings of Christmas presents for your partner.
I really want Yuna's present.
That's nice. I feel like I want to get a present too.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
Can we do this sometime soon?
Speaking of Christmas.
You all want presents.
Well, I don't know what I want anymore.
But I got earphones.
I read the letter and received earphones.
And then it started falling, saying “Shalala la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
I knew that if I made a wish, it might come true.
It means it might come true,
This means it could be a thing, right?
It can't be anything but a thing?
Just draw a thing and give it to him.
What do you want?
I want a picture, too. I have one right now.
There's one reason why it's a bit of a puzzle.
What? What is it?
Mr. Nakamura's illustrations that make everyone smile.
But maybe not everyone is smiling today.
No smiling faces?
What do you mean?
What would you like?
Wait a minute.
What do you think Yuna wants? What do you think they all want? What do you want?
What do you want? I'll lose it as soon as you ask me “What do you want?
I get it. I got it.
What is it?
SakuraiI've decided.
I definitely want this.
Always.
Nakamura decided, too.
Are you done? Yeah, I'm done. What? Why? I want this. Nakamura, I've decided too.
Are you done?
Yes, I'm done.
What?
Why?
I don't draw carefully.
I think the eyes on my face are the key.
That's true.
The eyes are the most important.
I don't enjoy being an artist.
What? You're early.
It's fine. Sakurayama is done.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
What should I do with this? Ready.
Se-no.
Here's your Christmas present.
Let's see, here's this.
Wait, what's this too? First.
No, no, no, first of all, this one. What's this?
What, you don't know?
A pond?
A phone chain.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What do you think, everyone? Yuma has a lot of knick-knacks,
I'm constantly replacing her phone chain.
I want to send her a phone chain this year, too.
Aika-san, you made a great movie with the curse on your hand.
But I'm very happy.
Really? I'm glad.
By the way, here it is,
You know what I mean.
You see, I know it now.
I know it now.
What do you think this is?
What's this?
Gummi.
I'm getting it now.
You know, apple gummies as they are?
Yes, yes, yes.
Just like “Sono Manma Ringo Gummi”.
Yeah, yeah. It looks like an apple. Is this apple gummy bear cut apple gummies? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just like apple gummies.
It looks like an apple.
This is an apple, representing a cut apple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
There are gummies shaped like this.
Mm-hmm.
And I gave one to Emma today.
That's right.
She said it was delicious.
Are they really delicious?
She was impressed, so I'll give it to her,
The reason I wasn't sure why I wanted to give it to her was because it was too cheap.
I see.
It's like Emma gave me a Christmas present and I felt bad about giving her a 200-yen one.
Wow, you really went that far.
After thinking about it, I came up with this one.
It's not a face.
What's the face?
I want to see his face. I want to see his face.
What do you mean? What do you mean? Eyes, eyes, eyebrows, mouth, laugh lines, laugh lines.
You see that, right? That's what I mean?
You drew it with intention. You can't draw with intention.
That's great. You mean like this?
So this is what you mean.
That's great.
It looks like a character. The one with arms and legs from the face.
That's for sure.
Now we've had a successful gift exchange.
This whole section is going to be over so easily.
Indeed.
Both of them proceeded to pan-pan-pan.
Do you want me to do this cola?
Just a little.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit,
How to get out of the futon on a cold morning.
I want you to tell me something.
Sure.
Yes.
SakuraiI really can't do this.
I can't do it either.
I'm not good at getting up.
I don't want to get up even if it's cold or hot. I understand. I can't get out of the futon. I can't either. I'm not good at getting up. I don't want to get up even if it's cold or hot.
I understand.
I don't want to get out of the futon.
It's impossible. I put my alarm on.
And that's my latest problem.
I spend so much time thinking that I fall asleep as soon as I get home.
That's true.
I understand.
I understand. I always say that I'm sure I'm going to fall asleep today.
What? I really do fall asleep right away. My brain can't keep up with my mouth.
I'm talking too fast, and I was talking again today about how I want to fix my fast talking,
I was talking again today about how I want to fix my fast-talking, but my mouth moves so fast that my brain can't keep up with it and short-circuits.
Then I get really tired and fall asleep.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's like a computer keyboard being hit too fast and too hard. My brain.
It's amazing, really.
It's amazing that your mouth is moving first.
Yes! My mouth moves first.
When I get to the halfway point, it's already out. All the way to the end.
So there's a little bit of a time lag, and my head gets really tired, so I sleep all the time.
What's with the alarm hot up?
It's my alarm evitur.
That's right. I'm telling you.
It's bad, right?
It's going to be bad. It's going to start.
Put your phone far away. That's right.
You say that.
I don't know, maybe it's just me,
I don't hear the alarm when it's on?
Yeah, so it's not like I'm stopping it.
I'm just saying.
It's not like I'm sleeping twice. No one wakes up even once to begin with.
Yeah. I wonder what it is.
I can't hear.
I don't hear them. And I've been asking my mom, too,
What time are you getting up tomorrow? What time do you get up? She asks me to wake up at that time,
And she tells me to wake up at that time, but I'm not saying that I don't want to wake up,
It's not that I don't want to get up, it's just that I can't. I'm not saying I'm lazy.
It's not that I'm lazy.
Why?
It's not that I don't want to go today, or that I'm sleepy, or that I'm going to sleep until I do.
It's just that I haven't made it back to the real world yet.
I wonder. I wonder what I should do. I don't know what to do.
Well, I wonder what I should do. That's what I'm saying,
I'm just saying, let's do our best,
It's really great that everyone wakes up every day in the cold.
So, that's it for this unpleasant and joyful December.
It's early, isn't it?
December will be over soon.
Only 11 more days to go. Ibn.
So, the 76th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Married Couple Showroom is coming to an end in the blink of an eye.
Yes, yes.
Shall we make an announcement?
I would like to make an announcement,
Yes, I would like to make an announcement.
The announcement is below.
Hmm?
Did you leave them there?
The announcements are, um, announcements?
We seem to have left the announcement card in the dressing room, so let me explain verbally.
Yes, I'll explain it verbally.
On January 4, 2024, at the Kobe Harborland Space Theater, we will be holding a performance of the Private Ebisu University Road to Saitama Free Love Tour. Thank you very much.
Wow, you are memorizing it, I am.
That's great.
Yes, I'll be waiting for you in Kobe.
I'll be waiting for you in Kobe, so let's say Happy New Year in person.
By all means.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all.
And then, and then, and then. And then and then and then,
And then, and then, and then,
Already, 2025,
The main event.
The main event, New Urban University's 15th anniversary University Performing Arts Festival 2025 Love&Brave will be held at Saitama Super Arena on March 20, 2025,
It will be held at Saitama Super Arena on March 20, 2025,
I want you all to come.
I really hope you all come.
We are really looking forward to seeing you all.
I am really looking forward to it.
Please come and enjoy the show.
Just three months away.
Just three more months.
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best. Let's do our best. Let's do our best. Okay, so before we get to the final rankings,
Here, I would like to close the ranking of Christmas tiki gifts, which I explained earlier in the opening, once and for all here.
Please understand that any gifting after this point will not be reflected in the ranking.
So, let's go to the countdown.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Deadline!
Thank you all for your comments and gifts.
So, the ranking is being counted now.
Thank you very much for your comments and gifts.
There are many.
It's great, isn't it?
Yes, it is. Like this.
You know...
It's too rare.
Rare, isn't it?
Ah shi.
Rare.
It's rare. It's rare. Let me put on this Santa Claus' clothes and do a little bit. Ash, ash, ash, ash.
It's rare, let me kiss this Santa Claus and do a little bit.
That's right, give him a little kiss.
I caught it!
I caught it, that I did.
Okay, Yuna, please!
Yes, Tomoki, in third place.
Thank you very much. 2nd place, Mr. Tomoki. Thank you very much.
Second place, Mr. Monta.
Thank you very much.
1st place, Chan-Tsushuko-san.
I'm very happy.
We would like to send our autographed checkee cards to the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners we have just called.
I would like to send them to you.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
And now, the final ranking,
I would like to announce everyone from 5th place to 1st place.
I have just announced them,
I'm sorry.
I was about to announce the top 20.
I was about to announce 20.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
So,
That's the end of the 76th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Unwindy Showroom.
We will inform you of the next installment as soon as it is decided.
That's all for now, Ebichu Private Junior High School.
Have a happy New Year. Me too. Me too. you you you